ganni.com 2019-06-08

# Privacy Policy

At GANNI we are very attentive to the need for appropriate protection and responsible processing of all personal information that we receive and we give data security and confidentiality high priority. This Personal Data Policy sets out clear guidelines for how GANNI will process your personal information and we update our policy on an ongoing basis, in accordance with internal processes and applicable legislation.

GANNI assures full confidentiality in respect of your personal data. We are responsible for personal data that is submitted via www.GANNI.com, and we will only disclose your information to third parties in connection with the service that we deliver to you.

The following is an account of how we use the personal information you leave and/or submit when you visit our website and when you use the various services on our website. 

#### Data controller and contact information

GANNI A/S  
Frederiksholms Kanal 4b  
1220 Copenhagen K  
Denmark

Danish Business Registration no. (CVR): 21664731

Tel.: (+45) 33 32 44 57 (weekdays from 10am - 5pm CET)  
Email: [legal@ganni.dk](mailto:legal@ganni.dk)

#### Collection of information

GANNI collects information about you when you actively submit information to www.GANNI.com, subscribe to the newsletter, place an order, participate in competitions and/or participate in other activities on the website. You will always be informed in connection with the collection of personal information about you. The personal information that we collect can include, for example, your name, your email address, your private address, your phone number and similar identification data, information about an online purchase and on your navigation of the website.

When submitting information, you will always be informed whether the input is voluntary or a requirement for the implementation of the desired action, such as completing a transaction in our webshop.

We collect your personal information in one or more of the following cases:

  *   * When you subscribe to GANNI's newsletter

  *   * When you take part in one of GANNI's competitions

Even if you use your email address in more than one of the above cases, your details will be only collected and registered in a single location. This allows your information to be reused, for example, when you make a purchase with us, while at the same time ensuring that you do not receive the same marketing material from GANNI more than once.

#### Subscribing to our newsletter

Entering your details and subscribing to the newsletter means that you are giving GANNI your consent to collect and process your personal information, for the purpose of sending you our newsletter. Only GANNI will receive and be able to access to your information and you may withdraw your consent.at any time. To find out more about your rights, please read our Personal Data Policy.

#### When you create a GANNI account

When you create an account with GANNI, your personal information will be processed in accordance with current personal data legislation. This means that your personal information is treated as confidential. The purpose of collecting your information is to create a GANNI account for you, where you can access your order history, see tracking links and proceed more quickly through the check out process. Completing the above form and creating an account means that you are granting your consent to GANNI’s collection, storage and usage of your personal information.

You may at any time contact us at any time at legal@ganni.com to obtain a copy of the personal information we have registered about you. In addition, you can always ask us to rectify incorrect information, delete or raise an objection to or limiting the processing of your information. If you have any questions about our processing of your information, you are also welcome to contact us at the above email address, or by telephone at (+45) 33 32 44 57. If you would like your entire GANNI account to be deleted, send an email to [customerservice@ganni.com](mailto:customerservice@ganni.com) at any time, asking us to delete your account.

Should you wish to lodge a complaint about our processing of your information, please contact the Danish Data Protection Agency. 

#### How we use personal information

Personal information is collected and used for the following purposes:

  * Fulfilment of an order in our webshop

  * Subscribing to a newsletter

  * Management of user account/profile

  * Participation in competitions or other events

  * Transmission of other marketing material, including invitations to events and the allocation of value codes

  * The collection and evaluation of consumer reviews

  * Summary of purchase history

  * Statistics and analysis of traffic on www.GANNI.com

  * Other marketing measures

We would like to point out that the use of your personal information for the sending of marketing material will only take place if you have previously submitted your explicit consent, unless the Act provides for the possibility of that we can contact you without you having given us your consent first.

GANNI maintains statistics about which areas of the website our users visit and what products are users’ favourites. These data does not contain personal information. The collected data gives us knowledge about how users use the website. This information is used to improve the website. We cannot see where you are visiting from or where you surf to on the Internet when you leave our site. We do not sell or in any other way disclose information about our users’ use and navigation of our website and we neither sell nor distribute information about your purchases to a third party. 

#### Disclosure to other data controllers

Your personal information will not be disclosed to a third party without your permission. However, under certain circumstances and in accordance with legislation, we may be required by law to disclose information to public authorities or the police. For example, we are required to disclose information to the police in cases of suspected credit card fraud.

#### Handover to other data processors

Information for use in the product delivery is handed over to the shipping company that GANNI is using. Your personal information is also passed on to GANNI’s partners who provide services on GANNI's behalf, such as in connection with the sending of newsletters. These partners only process personal information on GANNI's behalf and in accordance with GANNI's instructions.

In the case of restructuring or the total or partial sale of the company, any connected disclosure will be in compliance with legislation that is in force at that time, concerning the processing of personal data. 

#### Transfer to non-member (third party) states

Your personal information is transferred to the USA, as GANNI avails itself of the services of Salesforce, which has acceded to the so-called EU U.S Privacy Shield Framework. The Commission has ruled that the protection level is sufficient in the USA, once companies have acceded to the Privacy Shield Framework. For more information about Privacy Shield Framework, see [the official website](https://www.privacyshield.gov/welcome).

#### Deletion of personal information

We delete your personal information when we no longer need to process it in order to fulfil one or more of the purposes as stated in 4 above (how we use personal information). The information may, however, be processed and stored for longer than this, in an anonymised form.

#### Cookies

We use cookies on our website. You can read more about our use of cookies in our Cookie Policy, which you can find [here](https://www.ganni.com/en/customer-service/cookies-2/cookie-policy.html).

#### Your rights

We have implemented security measures to ensure that our internal procedures are compliant with our high security standards. We thus endeavour to protect the quality and integrity of your personal information.

#### Security

You are entitled to gain insight into the information that we process about you (subject to certain statutory exclusions). You are also entitled to raise objections to the collection and further processing of your personal information. Furthermore, you are entitled to have your personal information corrected, deleted or blocked, in accordance with relevant regulations You are additionally entitled to obtain information about yourself that you have given to us and to have this data transmitted to another data controller.

#### Revocation of consent

You may revoke any consent that you may have given us. We will then delete your information, unless we are able to continue processing on some other basis. If you would like to revoke your consent, please contact us at customerservice@ganni.com or (+45) 3332 4457 all weekdays between 10am - 5pm (CET).

#### Links to other websites etc.

Our website may contain links to other websites or to integrated web sites. We are not responsible for the content of other companies’ websites or for their practices in connection with the collection of personal information. When you visit other websites, we encourage you to read in the site owner's policy for the protection of personal information and other relevant policies.

#### Alteration and deletion of information etc.

If you would like us to update, amend or delete personal information that we have registered about you, if you would like access to the personal information that is processed about you, or if you have inquiries about the above guidelines, please contact us at customerservice@ganni.dk or on (+45) 33 32 44 57 on weekdays between 10am - 5pm CET.

You can also write to us at the following address:  
GANNI A/S  
Frederiksholms Kanal 4B  
1220 Copenhagen K  
Denmark 

#### How to lodge a complaint

If you would like to lodge a complaint about the processing of your personal information, please contact us by telephone or email, as presented above. You can also contact the Danish Data Protection Agency at Datatilsynet, Borgergade 28 5, DK 1300, Copenhagen K, Denmark.
